Guide to the Tim Smith Collection on The Saint MSS.418
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Sound recordings on disc, 1973-2000, undated
  - Don't Pity Me -- Faith Hope & Charity, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Don't Pity Me -- Faith Hope & Charity, 1978 (Box 10)
  - You're My Peace of Mind -- Faith Hope & Charity, 1978 (Box 10)
  - You're My Peace of Mind -- Faith Hope & Charity, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Wrap Your Arms Around Me -- Fltskog, Agnetha, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Fame -- Fame Soundtrack (Irene Cara), 1980 (Box 10)
  - Evergreen -- Fantasia, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Age Of Reason -- Farnham, John, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Age Of Reason -- Farnham, John, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Slave To Love -- Ferry, Bryan, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Don't Cry For Me Argentina -- Festival, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Don't Cry For Me Argentina -- Festival, 1979 (Box 10)
  - No Stars (Remix) -- Figures On A Beach, 1987 (Box 10)
  - No Stars (Remix) -- Figures On A Beach, 1987 (Box 10)
  - You Ain't Seen Nothing Yet (12" Club Mix) -- Figures On A Beach, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Don't Look Back -- Fine Young Canibals, 1989 (Box 10)
  - She Drives Me Crazy (The Justin Strauss Remix) -- Fine Young Cannibals, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Dr. Love -- First Choice, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Proze & Cons -- First Contact, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Precious Lies -- Five Sinners, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Precious Lies -- Five Sinners, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Precious Lies -- Five Sinners, 1982 (Box 10)
  - The Fool -- Fixx, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Big Love -- Fleetwood Mac, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Earthquake -- Flirtations, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Calling All Boys -- Flirts, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Now And Forever -- Florence, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Now And Forever -- Florence, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Groovy Feeling -- Fluke, Undated (Box 10)
  - Philly -- Fluke, Undated (Box 10)
  - Holding Out For A Hero -- Footloose Sountrack (Bonnie Tyler), Undated (Box 10)
  - Walk Away -- Foreman, Bonnie, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Who Loves You -- Four Seasons, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Who Loves You -- Four Seasons, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Precious Little Diamonds -- Fox the Fox, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Warriors Of The Wasteland (Turn The Knife Mix) -- Frankie Goes to Hollywood, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Warriors Of The Wasteland (Wild Disciples Mix) -- Frankie Goes to Hollywood, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Welcome To The Pleasuredome (12 XZTAS 7) -- Frankie Goes To Hollywood, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to the Pleasure Dome (Nalin & Kane Remix) -- Frankie Goes To Hollywood, 2000 (Box 10)
  - A Deeper Love (C&C Factory Mix) -- Franklin, Aretha, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Freeway Of Love -- Franklin, Aretha, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Get It Right -- Franklin, Aretha, Undated (Box 11)
  - Who's Zoomin' Who -- Franklin, Aretha, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Cloud 8 (Raid Mix) -- Frazier Chorus, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Nothing (Raid Mix) -- Frazier Chorus, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Typical -- Frazier Chorus, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Keep On Pumpin' It Up -- Freestyle Orchestra featuring D'Borah, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Baila Bolero (Dance Mix) -- Fun Fun, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Color My Love -- Fun Fun, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Keep On Dancin' -- Gary's Gang, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Knock Me Out -- Gary's Gang, 1982 (Box 11)
  - I Am What I Am -- Gaynor, Gloria, Undated (Box 11)
  - I Am What I Am -- Gaynor, Gloria, Undated (Box 11)
  - I Will Survive -- Gaynor, Gloria, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Never Can Say Goodbye -- Gaynor, Gloria, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Love In Your Eyes -- Gazebo, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Masterpiece -- Gazebo, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Masterpiece -- Gazebo, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Que Sera Mi Vida (If You Should Go) -- Gibson Brothers, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Feel It -- Gilles, Samantha, Undated (Box 11)
  - Secret Love -- Gilles, Samantha, 1986 (Box 11)
  - I Haven't Stopped Dancin' -- Gonzales, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Rain -- Goombay Dance Band, 1980 (Box 11)
  - I Want To Live -- Grace, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Not Over Yet -- Grace, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Walking On Sunshine -- Grant, Eddy, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Flotation -- Grid, The, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Step By Step -- Griffin, Peter, 1980 (Box 11)
  - The Best Part Of Breakin' Up -- Griffith, Roni, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Play To Win -- Gung-Ho, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Close To You (Larry Levan Remix) -- Guthrie, Gwen, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Close To You (Larry Levan Remix) -- Guthrie, Gwen, 1986 (Box 11)
  - On The Road To Mandalay -- Harlow, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Hearts On Fire -- Harris, Sam, 1984 (Box 11)
  - I Want That Man (12" Remix) -- Harry, Deborah, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Instant Replay (A Tom Moulton Mix) -- Hartman, Dan, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Instant Replay (A Tom Moulton Mix) -- Hartman, Dan, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Vertigo/Relight My Fire -- Hartman, Dan, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Vertigo/Relight My Fire -- Hartman, Dan, 1979 (Box 11)
  - We Are The Young -- Hartman, Dan, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Let Me Go! -- Heaven 17, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Big Love (Original) -- Heller, Pete, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Keep On Rockin' -- Hemyl, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Keep It Confidential -- Hendryx, Nona, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Born To Be Alive -- Hernandez, Patrick, 1979 (Box 11)
  - You'll Never Know -- Hi-Gloss, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Sweet Dreams -- Hip On Ice, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Into The Fire -- Hit List, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Give Me A Little Inspiration -- Holloway, Brenda, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Love Sensation (Shep Pettibone Mix) -- Holloway, Loleatta, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Seconds -- Holloway, Loleatta, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Love Is To Love A Lover's Love -- Hot Shot, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Saturday Night, Sunday Morning -- Houston, Thelma, 1978 (Box 11)
  - I Learned From The Best -- Houston, Whitney, 1998 (Box 11)
  - It's Not Right But It's Okay -- Houston, Whitney, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Love Will Save The Day -- Houston, Whitney, 1987 (Box 12)
  - So Emotional (Mike Carroll Edit) -- Houston, Whitney, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Throwin' It All Away -- Hughes, Rhetta, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Human -- Human, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Human -- Human, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Don't You Want Me -- Human League, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Don't You Want Me -- Human League, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Heart Like A Wheel (Extended Mix) -- Human League, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Hearts On Fire (Extended Re-Mix) -- Hush, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Tokio Rose -- Idle Eyes, 1984 (Box 12)
  - White Wedding -- Idol, Billy, 1982 (Box 12)
  - White Wedding -- Idol, Billy, 1982 (Box 12)
  - White Wedding -- Idol, Billy, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Be With You (Thunderpuss Club) -- Iglesias, Enrique, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Just An Illusion -- Imagination, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Stay With Me -- India, 1983 (Box 12)
  - I Don't Wanna Go On With You Like That -- John, Elton, 1988 (Box 12)
  - What A Night (Dance Version Remix) -- Iten, Terry, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Shut Out Medley -- Jabara, Paul, 1977 (Box 12)
  - When I Think Of You -- Jackson, Janet, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Child Of Tomorrow -- Johnson, Kevin, 1984 (Box 12)
  - When I Think Of You (Dance Remix) -- Jackson, Janet, 1986 (Box 12)
  - When The Rain Begins To Fall -- Jackson, Jermaine & Pia Zadora, Undated (Box 12)
  - Billy Jean -- Jackson, Michael, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Thriller -- Jackson, Michael, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Right In The Night (Original 12") -- Jam & Spoon, 1994 (Box 12)
  - The Complete Stella -- Jam & Spoon, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Glad To Know You -- Jankel, Chas, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Love Don't Cost A Thing (HQ2 Club Vocal Mix) -- Jennifer Lopez, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Hit 'N Run Lover -- Jiani, Carol, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Let's Not Say Goodbye (Sky High Dub Mix) -- Jigsaw, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Sky High -- Jigsaw, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Sky High -- Jigsaw, 1989 (Box 12)
  - I Don't Wanna Go On With You Like That -- John, Elton, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Shattered Dreams (12" Extended Mix) -- Johnny Hates Jazz, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Heaven's Here -- Johnson, Holly, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Come To Me -- Joli, France, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Girl In The 80's -- Joli, France, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Standing In The Shadows Of Love -- Joli, France, 1983 (Box 12)
  - The Heart To Break The Heart -- Joli, France, Undated (Box 12)
  - Last Call -- Jolo, 1984 (Box 12)
  - I Need A Man -- Jones, Grace, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Nights Over Egypt -- Jones Girls, 1981 (Box 12)
  - I Need A Man -- Jones, Grace, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Nights Over Egypt -- Jones Girls, 1981 (Box 12)
  - I'm Not Perfect (Remix) -- Jones, Grace, 1986 (Box 12)
  - My Heart's Not In It -- Jones, Brenda, 1982 (Box 12)
  - I'll Find My Way To You -- Jones, Grace, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Tonight I'm Gonna Make You A Star -- Jones, Brenda, 1983 (Box 12)
  - I'll Find My Way To You -- Jones, Grace, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Below The Belt -- Jones, Grace, Undated (Box 12)
  - Party Girl -- Jones, Grace, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Slave To The Rhythm -- Jones, Grace, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Walking In The Rain -- Jones, Grace, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Private Life -- Jones, Grace, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Shades Of Summer -- Jones, Rodeo, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Getting To The Heart Of Me -- Juvet, Patrick, 1983 (Box 13)
  - I Love America -- Juvet, Patrick, 1978 (Box 13)
  - After Tea -- Kama Sutra, Undated (Box 13)
  - Storm In My Soul (Long) -- Kama Sutra, 1996 (Box 13)
  - On Fire -- Kane, Madleen, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Playing For Time (Special 12" Version) -- Kane, Madleen, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Secret Love Affair -- Kane, Madleen, Undated (Box 13)
  - You Can (Special 12" Verision) -- Kane, Madleen, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Another Life -- Kano, 1983 (Box 13)
  - The Break (Dance Remix) -- Katmandu, 1987 (Box 13)
  - The Break (Remix) -- Katmandu, 1980 (Box 13)
  - You Said You'D Gimme Some More -- KC & The Sunshine Band, Undated (Box 13)
  - Magic Fly -- Kebe Kelektrik, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Africa -- Key of Dreams, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Love Come Down -- King, Evelyn, 1982 (Box 13)
  - I Need A Man In My Life -- Kissoon, Katie, Undated (Box 13)
  - I Need A Man In My Life -- Kissoon, Katie, Undated (Box 13)
  - Where Is My Man -- Kitt, Eartha, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Cha Cha Heels -- Kitt, Eartha & Bronski Beat, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Never Knew Love Like This Before -- Klausenn, Tina, Undated (Box 13)
  - You Bring Out The Best In Me -- Knight, Gladys, 1979 (Box 13)
  - You Bring Out The Best In Me -- Knight, Gladys, 1979 (Box 13)
  - I Will Fight -- Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Taste Of Bitter Love -- Knight, Gladys & The Pips, Undated (Box 13)
  - Shockwave (Special Mix) -- Knopfler, David, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Shockwave (Special Mix) -- Knopfler, David, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Shockwave (Steven Von Blau Remix) -- Knopfler, David, 1985 (Box 13)
  - The Whistle Song (Sound Factory 12" Mix) -- Knuckles, Frankie, 1991 (Box 13)
  - The Whistle Song (Sound Factory 12" Mix) -- Knuckles, Frankie, 1991 (Box 13)
  - I Beg Your Pardon -- Kon Kan, Undated (Box 13)
  - Autobahn -- Kraftwerk, Undated (Box 13)
  - Electric Caf -- Kraftwerk, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Trans Europe Express -- Kraftwerk, Undated (Box 13)
  - Baby I Don't Know -- Kryptonite, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Please Don't Go -- K.W.S., 1992 (Box 13)
  - Certain Things Are Likely (Original) -- KTP, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Stand Up -- KTP, Undated (Box 13)
  - I'll Cry For You -- Kumano, 1984 (Box 13)
  - New Attitude -- LaBelle, Patti, Undated (Box 13)
  - Fly Away / Walking in the Sunshine -- Laid Back, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Love Is On The Rocks -- Lama, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Love Is On The Rocks (DX) -- Lama, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Harmony -- Lane, Suzi, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Miss Chatelaine (St. Tropez) -- Lang, k.d., 1992 (Box 13)
  - Keep On Talking -- LaPorte, Carrie, 1980 (Box 13)
  - American Love -- Laurens, Rose, 1986 (Box 13)
  - American Love ('87 Remix) -- Laurens, Rose, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Night Sky -- Laurens, Rose, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Night Sky -- Laurens, Rose, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Doin' The Best That I Can -- LaVette, Bettye, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Doin' The Best That I Can -- LaVette, Bettye, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Follow Me (Siamese) -- Lear, Amanda, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Follow Me ('89 High Energy) -- Lear, Amanda, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Love Your Body -- Lear, Amanda, 1983 (Box 14)
  - The Men In My Life -- Lee, Miriam, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Maybe This Time -- Lewis, Norma, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Invitation -- Life Force, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Don't You Treat Me Like A Lover -- Lift, The, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Never Ending Story (12" Mix) -- Limahl, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Angel Eyes (Remix) -- Lime, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Babe, We're Gonna Love Tonight -- Lime, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Come And Get Your Love -- Lime, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Come And Get Your Love -- Lime, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Guilty (Long Remix) -- Lime, 1983 (Box 14)
  - On The Grid (Re-Mix) -- Lime, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Unexpected Lovers (Remix) -- Lime, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Wake Dream (Remix) -- Lime, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Your Love -- Lime, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Your Love (Remix) -- Lime, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Where Love Lives (Mo Knuckles) -- Limerick, Alison, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Where Love Lives (Mo Knuckles) -- Limerick, Alison, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Where Love Lives (Classic) -- Limerick, Alison, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Where Love Lives (Classic) -- Limerick, Alison, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Choir Practice -- Lipps, Inc., 1983 (Box 14)
  - My Baby's Baby -- Liquid Gold, 1979 (Box 14)
  - My Baby's Baby -- Liquid Gold, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Jump Shout (Remix) -- Lisa, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Rocket To My Heart -- Lisa, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Tempt Me -- Lisa, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Daydream Believer (Extended Mix) -- Local Hero, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Lover You Send Me Colors -- London Beat, Undated (Box 14)
  - You Don't Need Someone New -- Lotus Eaters, 1983 (Box 14)
  - You Don't Need Someone New -- Lotus Eaters, 1983 (Box 14)
  - How Much, How Much I Love You -- Love and Kisses, 1978 (Box 14)
  - You Must Be Love -- Love and Kisses, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Miami Heatwave -- Love Twins, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Love's Theme -- Love Unlimited, Undated (Box 14)
  - Extraterrestrial Lover -- Love, Sylvia, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Backstreet Romance -- Loverde, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Die Hard Lover -- Loverde, 1982 (Box 14)
  - I Gotta Keep Dancin' -- Lucas, Carrie, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Shake It Up Tonight -- Lynn, Cheryl, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Excited (M People Master Mix) -- M People, 1992 (Box 14)
  - How Can I Love You More (Classic) -- M People, 1991 (Box 14)
  - This Is Paradise -- M.B.G., Undated (Box 14)
  - There But For The Grace Of God -- Machine, 1978 (Box 14)
  - There But For The Grace Of God -- Machine, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Yesterday's Men -- Madness, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Deeper and Deeper (Shep Pettibone Classic 12" Mix) -- Madonna, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Justify My Love (12" Orbit) -- Madonna, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Justify My Love (12" Orbit) -- Madonna, 1990 (Box 14)
  - La Isla Bonita (Extended Remix) -- Madonna, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Like A Prayer (Shep Pettibone 12" Dance Mix) -- Madonna, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Material Girl (John Jellybean Benitez Extended Dance Remix) -- Madonna, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Music (Calderone) -- Madonna, 2000 (Box 15)
  - Secret (Junior's Sound Factory) -- Madonna, 1994 (Box 15)
  - Vogue (Shep Pettibone 12" Version) -- Madonna, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Magnifique -- Magnifique, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Magnifique (Bob Viteritti Mix) -- Magnifique, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Magnifique (Siamese) -- Magnifique, Undated (Box 15)
  - City Nights (Hot Tracks - Greg Silvia Edit) -- Manchester, Melissa, Undated (Box 15)
  - Back In My Arms Again -- Manley, Cynthia, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Summertime -- Marquee, Danny featuring Matta Jones, 1990 (Box 15)
  - 18 Carat Garbage -- Martin, Billie Ray, Undated (Box 15)
  - Honey -- Martin, Billie Ray, Undated (Box 15)
  - Systems of Silence -- Martin, Billie Ray, Undated (Box 15)
  - Lonely Love -- Martin, John, Undated (Box 15)
  - Take It Slowly -- Martinez, Nancy, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Take It Slowly -- Martinez, Nancy, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Take It Slowly (12") -- Martinez, Nancy, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Stay -- Marx & Spencer, 2000 (Box 15)
  - Begin The Beguine -- Mathis, Johnny, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Begin The Beguine -- Mathis, Johnny, 1979 (Box 15)
  - La Dolce Vita -- Matisse, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Shine On Silver Moon -- McCoo, Marilyn & Billy Davis Jr., 1978 (Box 15)
  - Ain't No Stoppin' Us Now -- McFadden & Whitehead, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Won't You Let Me Be The One -- McGloiry, Michael, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Let The Night Take The Blame -- McKane, Lorraine, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Deep In Vogue -- McLaren, Malcolm, Undated (Box 15)
  - I Got The Message -- Men Without Hats, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Pop Goes The World -- Men Without Hats, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Disco Dance (Disco Mix) -- Michele, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Memory -- Menage, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Wind Beneath My Wings -- Menage, 1985 (Box 15)
  - I Was Born To Love You (Steven Von Blau Mix) -- Mercury, Freddie, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Love Kills -- Mercury, Freddie, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Catch The Rhythm -- Midney, Boris, 1979 (Box 15)
  - All I Need Is A Miracle -- Mike and the Mechanics, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Bit By Bit -- Mills, Stephanie, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Losing My Mind (Remix) -- Minnelli, Liza, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Deeper N Deeper (Ultimix) -- Modern Rocketry, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Homosexuality -- Modern Rocketry, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Thank God For Men -- Modern Rocketry, 1985 (Box 15)
  - You're My Heart, You're My Soul -- Modern Talking, 1985 (Box 15)
  - You're My Heart, You're My Soul -- Modern Talking, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Lady (Hear Me Tonight) -- Modjo, 2000 (Box 15)
  - Fallen Angel -- Monday, 1988 (Box 15)
  - I'm Not In Love (Drum Version) -- Monroe, George, 1987 (Box 15)
  - I Need Your Love -- Montana, June, 1989 (Box 15)
  - I Need Your Love -- Montana, June, 1989 (Box 15)
  - I Need Your Love (Te Quiero) -- Montana, June, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Blue World -- Moody Blues, 1983 (Box 15)
  - I Know You're Out There Somewhere (Remix) -- Moody Blues, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Just Another Broken Heart -- Moore, Dorothy, 1984 (Box 15)
  - How's Your Love Life Baby -- Moore, Jackie, 1979 (Box 15)
  - This Is It -- Moore, Melba, Undated (Box 15)
  - Strange Day For Dancing -- Moral Support, 1984 (Box 15)
  - From Here To Eternity -- Moroder, Georgio, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Call Me (Theme from American Gigolo) -- Moroder, Georgio, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Chase -- Moroder, Georgio, 1978 (Box 16)
  - From Here To Eternity -- Moroder, Georgio, Undated (Box 16)
  - If You Weren't Afraid -- Moroder, Georgio, Undated (Box 16)
  - If You Weren't Afraid -- Moroder, Georgio, Undated (Box 16)
  - Knights In White Satin -- Moroder, Georgio, Undated (Box 16)
  - Love's In You, Love's In Me -- Moroder, Georgio & Chris, Undated (Box 16)
  - Together In Electric Dreams -- Moroder, Giorgio with Philip Oakey, 1984 (Box 16)
  - All Cried Out -- Moyet, Alison, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Broken Wings -- Mr. Mister, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Keep On Jumpin' -- Musique, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Hold On To This Moment -- Mystery, 1986 (Box 16)
  - That's The Way Love Is -- Nail, Jimmy, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Don't Stop The Train -- Nelson, Phyllis, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Don't Stop The Train (Jim Burgess Remix) -- Nelson, Phyllis, 1981 (Box 16)
  - I Like You -- Nelson, Phyllis, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Round & Round -- New Order, 1989 (Box 16)
  - True Faith -- New Order, Undated (Box 16)
  - Love Is In You -- Nightlife Unlimited, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Only Baby (Be For Me) -- No-Man, Undated (Box 16)
  - Silent Morning -- Noel, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Kind of Life (Kind of Love) -- North End, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Native New Yorker -- Odyssey, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Magic -- Olivia Newton-John, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Magic -- Olivia Newton-John, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dreaming -- Orchestral Manoeuvres, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Lookin' Out -- Orlando, Bobby (Bobby "O"), 1983 (Box 16)
  - She Has A Way -- Orlando, Bobby (Bobby "O"), 1982 (Box 16)
  - These Memories -- Orlando, Bobby (Bobby "O"), 1983 (Box 16)
  - Rise Up -- Parachute Club, 1983 (Box 16)
  - All On You -- Paris Angels, 1990 (Box 16)
  - All On You -- Paris Angels, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Dolce Vita -- Paris, Ryan, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Dolce Vita (Able) -- Paris, Ryan, Undated (Box 16)
  - Like An Eagle -- Parker, Dennis, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Pushin Too Hard -- Parker, Paul, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Right On Target -- Parker, Paul, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Shot In The Night -- Parker, Paul, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Time After Time -- Parker, Paul, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Heatstroke (LP Version) -- Parrish, Man, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Heatstroke (Ram's Horn Version) -- Parrish, Man, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Eye In The Sky -- Parsons Project, Alan, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Baby I'm Burnin' (Pink Vinyl) -- Parton, Dolly, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Potential New Boyfriend -- Parton, Dolly, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Potential New Boyfriend -- Parton, Dolly, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Potential New Boyfriend -- Parton, Dolly, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Save The Last Dance For Me (Long Version) -- Parton, Dolly, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Hot Leather (Moby Mix Version) -- Passengers, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Use It Up And Wear It Out -- Pat & Mick, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Oh No No (Robbie Leslie Mix) -- Paul, Bernie, 1981 (Box 16)
  - The Two Of Us -- Jones, Ronny & Claudja Barry, 1981 (Box 16)
  - I'm Not In Love/Girl, You're In Love (Vocal) -- Payne, Scherrie, 1982 (Box 16)
  - I'm Not In Love/Girl, You're In Love (Vocal) -- Payne, Scherrie, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Don't Make Me Wait (Extended Version) -- Peech Boys, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Pistol In My Pocket -- Pellay, Lana, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Heartache (Remix) -- Pepsi and Shirlie, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Not At Home to Heartache (The Majestic Mix) -- Perfect Alibi, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Not At Home to Heartache (The Majestic Mix) -- Perfect Alibi, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Not At Home to Heartache (The Majestic Mix) -- Perfect Alibi, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Always On My Mind (12") -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Heart (Dance Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - I Want A Dog (EMI) (LP Version) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - I Wouldn't Normally Do This Kind Of Thing (Wild Tribal) -- Pet Shop Boys, Undated (Box 17)
  - It's A Sin (Disco Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Always On My Mind-In My House (LP Version) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1996 (Box 17)
  - Left To My Own Devices (Disco Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Left To My Own Devices (Disco Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Left To My Own Devices (Disco Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Left To My Own Devices (Shep Pettibone Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Rent (Extended Remix) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Love Comes Quickly (Dance Mix) -- Pet Shop Boys, Undated (Box 17)
  - Where The Streets Have No Name (I Can't Take My Eyes Off You) -- Pet Shop Boys, 1991 (Box 17)
  - City Lights (Vocal) -- Pitt, William, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Funny Girl -- Pitt, William, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Sex -- Pleasure & The Beast, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Sex -- Pleasure & The Beast, 1984 (Box 17)
  - I Need You -- Pointer Sisters, 1983 (Box 17)
  - I'm So Excited -- Pointer Sisters, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Jump (For My Love) -- Pointer Sisters, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Someday We'll Be Together -- Pointer Sisters, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Heaven Must Have Sent You -- Pointer, Bonnie, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Take It Back -- Pookah Makes Three, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Looking For Atlantis -- Prefab Sprout, 1990 (Box 17)
  - The Golden Calf -- Prefab Sprout, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Duel -- Propaganda, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Machinery -- Propaganda, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Machinery -- Propaganda, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Heartbeat -- Psychedelic Furs, Undated (Box 17)
  - Love Taker -- Pulga, Stephano, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Love Taker (Raul & Steven Mix) -- Pulga, Stephano, 1983 (Box 17)
  - We Can Make It -- Purple Flash, 1984 (Box 17)
  - The Sun Ain't Gonna Shine Anymore -- Quantize, 1988 (Box 17)
  - A La Vie, A L'Amour -- Quartz, Jackie, 1987 (Box 17)
  - No Regrets (Musclebound Mix) -- Quartzlock, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Close Your Eyes -- Queen Samantha, 1983 (Box 17)
  - I Can Fly (Steven Von Blau Edit) -- Rainey, 1985 (Box 17)
  - In The Evening -- Ralph, Sheryl Lee, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Catch Me I'm Falling In Love -- Raven, Marcia, 1983 (Box 17)
  - You'll Never Find Another Love Like Mine -- Rawls, Lou, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Got To Have Loving -- Ray, Don, 1978 (Box 17)
  - All Summer Long (Jos Padilla & DJ Pippi Remix) -- Rea, Chris, 2000 (Box 17)
  - All Summer Long (The Katcha Remix) -- Rea, Chris, 2000 (Box 17)
  - I Can Hear Your Heartbeat -- Rea, Chris, 1983 (Box 17)
  - I Can Hear Your Heartbeat -- Rea, Chris, 1983 (Box 17)